{
    "id": "f4657c27597c44afa2ed59eca847e20c",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………………. my sons can drive.",
            "description": "We use neither of before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "Neither of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. them was there.",
            "description": "We use neither of before a pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "Neither of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… answer is correct.",
            "description": "Neither is used without of before a noun without a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "Neither of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "‘I can’t dance.’ ‘………………………. can I.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "‘She can’t swim.’ ‘I can’t ………………………’",
            "description": "Can’t either means the same as neither can.",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t travel ………………………… these days.",
            "description": "Much can be used as an adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "a lot",
                "very much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t got ……………………….. time.",
            "description": "Plenty of is mainly used in affirmative clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "plenty of",
                "much",
                "very much"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She has got ……………………………. women friends but she doesn’t know …………………..  men.",
            "description": "Many is mainly used in negative and interrogative sentences. In affirmative clauses we prefer plenty of or a lot of.",
            "answers": [
                "many, a lot of",
                "many, many",
                "a lot of, many"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You haven’t eaten ………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "a lot",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. cheese is made from cow milk.",
            "description": "We use most before a noun without a determiner. ",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Much",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… my friends are non-smokers.",
            "description": "We use most of before a noun with a determiner. ",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Most of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I won’t pass the exam. I could not answer ………………………….. the questions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "many of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}